[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much money does Nick Fisher owe Slim Hopkins/The Boss in Lucky Number Slevin?", "correct_answer": "$96,000", "incorrect_answers": ["$68,000", "$82,000", "$104,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This industrial facility, sometimes called a \u2018tank farm\u2019 or a \u2018terminal\u2019, is used for the storage of oil.", "correct_answer": "Oil depot", "incorrect_answers": ["Oil gusher", "Oil barrel", "Oil well"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The concept of Men in Black (men dressed in black suits claiming to be government agents) can be observed in all of these movies except one.", "correct_answer": "Memento", "incorrect_answers": ["A Beautiful Mind", "The Matrix", "Men In Black"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Arthurian legend, Queen Guineveres love affair with this knight of the Round Table led to the downfall of Camelot.", "correct_answer": "Lancelot", "incorrect_answers": ["Tristan", "Percival", "Galahad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Tenacious D, the initials JB stand for Jack Black.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Mimic Leatherjacket, found in the tropical marine waters throughout the Indo-Pacific, mimics which poisonous fish?", "correct_answer": "Saddled Puffer", "incorrect_answers": ["Red Bass", "Hogfish", "Stonefish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Academy Awards did the 1997 blockbuster Titanic win out of fourteen nominations?", "correct_answer": "Eleven", "incorrect_answers": ["Fourteen", "Nine", "Seven"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What positive effect do shiitake mushrooms, largely used in traditional Chinese medicine, have on human health?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They boost the immune system.", "They prevent cancer.", "They lower cholesterol."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first person to reach both the North and South Poles?", "correct_answer": "Roald Amundsen", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Falcon Scott", "Robert Peary", "Ernest Shackleton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fill in the missing word in this line from the movie Rocky IV: Its ....................! Youve seen him, you know how strong he is. You cant win!", "correct_answer": "Suicide", "incorrect_answers": ["Dumb", "Craziness", "Stupidity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of animal is a mudpuppy?", "correct_answer": "salamander", "incorrect_answers": ["skink", "eel", "fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Early on in the movie Walk the Line Johnny Cash enlists in what branch of the military?", "correct_answer": "Airforce", "incorrect_answers": ["Marines", "Army", "Navy"]}]